[{"answer": "Hello", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Hey.  Its Kim", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Hello", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Hey.  How are you", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Hey.  Its Kim", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Im doing great.  How about you", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Hey.  How are you", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Im pretty good", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Im doing great.  How about you", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Hows school", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Im pretty good", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Oh, you know.  Busy.  Ive been studying a lot for the final exams coming up", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Hows school", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Yes, I am ready.  Im finishing up my final papers.  Im so tired of it too.  It seem", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Oh, you know.  Busy.  Ive been studying a lot for the final exams coming up", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " I understand completely.  So, what else is new", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Yes, I am ready.  Im finishing up my final papers.  Im so tired of it too.  It seem", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": "Well, I met someone", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 31, "question": " I understand completely.  So, what else is new", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Really?  When did this happen", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Well, I met someone", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " About three months ago", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Really?  When did this happen", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " OK, well tell me all the details.  Who is this guy", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 34, "question": " About three months ago", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Well, his name is Jim and hes an architect", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 35, "question": " OK, well tell me all the details.  Who is this guy", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Wow!  An architect.  You mean hes studying Architecture at your school", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Well, his name is Jim and hes an architect", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " No, hes an actual architect.  Andhes 40", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Wow!  An architect.  You mean hes studying Architecture at your school", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " 40?  Thats a 15-year age difference.  Isnt it a little strange dating a guy tha", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 38, "question": " No, hes an actual architect.  Andhes 40", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " No, it never really seems like were different ages.  We just get along so well that ", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 42, "question": " 40?  Thats a 15-year age difference.  Isnt it a little strange dating a guy tha", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " How did you guys meet", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 47, "question": " No, it never really seems like were different ages.  We just get along so well that ", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Its funny, actually.  We met on a blind date.  It was the first one Id ever been on", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 48, "question": " How did you guys meet", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " How long have you been dating", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Its funny, actually.  We met on a blind date.  It was the first one Id ever been on", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Three months.  We are in love, its unbelievable", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 54, "question": " How long have you been dating", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Arent you moving a little fast?  How do you know you love him if its only bee", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Three months.  We are in love, its unbelievable", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " I know, I know it seems fast.  But, I just have this feeling, and I know its love", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Arent you moving a little fast?  How do you know you love him if its only bee", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Wow!  Thats great.  Im happy for you.  Are you guys engaged already", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 63, "question": " I know, I know it seems fast.  But, I just have this feeling, and I know its love", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " No, were not engaged.  But weve talked about marriage a lot, and he definitel", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Wow!  Thats great.  Im happy for you.  Are you guys engaged already", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Are you moving in with him or are you guys getting a new place", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 71, "question": " No, were not engaged.  But weve talked about marriage a lot, and he definitel", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Jim just bought a house, so were both going to move into that together.  It will b", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Are you moving in with him or are you guys getting a new place", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Thats so exciting.  Im really happy for you, Kim.  Have you told your parents", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Jim just bought a house, so were both going to move into that together.  It will b", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " No, not yet.  Im going home this weekend and I think Jim might come with me t", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Thats so exciting.  Im really happy for you, Kim.  Have you told your parents", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Well, I cant wait to meet him too", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 82, "question": " No, not yet.  Im going home this weekend and I think Jim might come with me t", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Maybe after graduation you could come stay with us and meet him", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Well, I cant wait to meet him too", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Sure.  Thatd be a nice break", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Maybe after graduation you could come stay with us and meet him", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " OK, well good luck with the last few weeks.  Call me next month and lets pla", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Sure.  Thatd be a nice break", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " OK.  Good luck to you too.  Good luck with your parents", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 89, "question": " OK, well good luck with the last few weeks.  Call me next month and lets pla", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Thanks.  Bye", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 90, "question": " OK.  Good luck to you too.  Good luck with your parents", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "07-06", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Thanks.  Bye", "qSentId": 90}]
